Guide to the Records of National Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated, 1949, 1954, 1956, 1958-1993 *I-181 and *I-181A
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Part 2, Series V: USSR Travel, Committee Files, and Reports, undated, 1970-1991; Boxes 54-91.
  - Subseries A: Individual Travel Reports, undated, 1970-1971, 1973-1989; Boxes 54-77.
    - Eklove, Joyce (Spring '86), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Elkins, Dov Peretz, Rabbi (10/88), 1988 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Emes, David D. (1/4/76-1/18/76), 1976 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Emmerich, Adam and Kessler, Daniel (11/10/86-11/29/86), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Epstein, David and Jeremy (8/3/87-8/12/87), 1987 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Eskin, Andrew and Sandra (8/5/84-8/18/84), 1984 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Eth, Charlotte B. and Daniel, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Everett, Bob and Prince, Edward (5/28/87-6/8/87), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fahn, Roberta and Wall, Harry (10/11/86-10/27/86), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Farber, Leonard (9/85), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Farber, Samuel and Phyllis, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Feldman, Albert (9/8/75-9/29/75), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Feldman, Elana and Aaron (9/23/89-10/1/89), 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Feldman, Shari and Gork, Lara (5/29/88-6/12/88), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Feltoon, Arnie (1/6/75-1/27/75), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Fenster, Irene and Irving (8/87), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Fenton, Tamar, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Fidler, Rhoda and Jay (9/2/88-9/16/88), 1988 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Fields, Rabbi Harvey (7/86), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Fierst, Edith (6/86), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Fine, Seymour H. and Adele (7/20/85-8/10/85), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Finegold, Rae, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Finkelstein, Leo (10/1/86-10/16/86), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Finkelstein, Nisson A. (6/24/76-7/8/76), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Fischer, Ethel ('89), 1989 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Fish, Hamilton, Congressman (5/75), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Fishbein, Barbara and Irwin (12/87), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Fishel, John R., 1988 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Fisher, Enid and Alexander ('87), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Fishman, Bob (1/5/79-1/13/79), 1979 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Fishman, Lyle and Altshul, William, Rabbi (11/1985), 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Flanzbaums (12/21/84-12/28/84), 1984 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Flumen, Audrey and Louis (7/9/89-7/22/89), 1989 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Flumenbaum, Judy (9/86), 1986 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Foxman, Mr. and Mrs. Abraham H. (12/4/74-12/18/74), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Frankel, Judge Marvin (7/6/74-7/21/74), 1974, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Franklin, Rabbi Wayne M., 1989 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Fraser, David (1/87), 1987 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Freedman, Joyce T., Ph.D., 1987 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Freedman, Robert O., Dr., 1975, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Freeman, Herb, Prof. (5/75), 1975 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Freilich, Dr. and Mrs. Dennis B. (6/3/73-6/17/73), 1973 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Freiman, Morton and Tina (5/13/75-5/26/75), 1975 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Freund, Henry and Joyce (7/9/89-7/24/89), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Friedman, Abe W. (3/88), 1988 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Friedman, Elaine and Arnie (8/88), 1988 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Friedman, Herbert and Grace, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Frisch School (12/88), undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Frishwasser, Drs. Ed and Mary (11/75), 1975 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Fromberg, Zachary and Jean (9/6/87-9/16/87), 1987 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Galinson, Elaine and Murray, April 9-20, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Gallo, Dean A., 1986 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Gannon, Dennis (5/7/76-5/22/76), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Garber, Dr. Delott (12/23/75), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Garfinkel, Essie and Raven, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Gelfond, Dr. and Mrs. Philip (4/21/85-5/5/85), undated, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Geller, David, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Geller, Kenneth, A., M.D., 1987 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Geller, Susan and Goldstein, Marilyn (7/89), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Gering, Claire and George, undated (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Gerson, Garry, Rabbi, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Gerwin, Daniel and Reck, Debbie, undated (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Getman's (7/83), 1983 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Gibbs, Laurie (10/18/86-10/26/86), 1986 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Giesberg, Middie, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Gifford, Dr. Bernard; Lachman, Dr. Seymour; Lynch, Dr. Gerald (Spring 1977), 1979 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Gilbert, Patsy K. (5/76), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Gilens, Alvin H. (12/76), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Gingold, Dr. Bruce and Miriam, undated (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Ginsburg, Barbara, Caroline, Ellen, Jane (12/27/86-1/3/87), 1987 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Ginsburg, Dr. Eli and Rochelle, undated, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Ginsburg, Ted and Natalie (7/8/87-7/20/87), 1987 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Gittelson, Abraham and Shulamit (7/23/74-8/11/74), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Glaser, Tom (10/89), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Glass, Judy and Mike (5/87), 1987 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Glatstein, Carol Cohan and Philip (3/18/89-3/25/89), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Glazer, Andrew et al. (4/85), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Glazer, Andrew, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Glickstein, Dr. Arthur and Bev (10/18/87-10/26/87), 1987 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Glikburg, Charlene and Bill, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Glucoft, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Glustrom, Helen and Simon (12/87), 1988 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Gold, Michael and Katz, James (7/1/73-7/19/73) (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Goldberg, Amy (10/87), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Goldberg, Harriet (Summer '79), 1980 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Goldberg, Leonard and Lucille (6/19/88-7/9/88) (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Goldberg, Rabbi Elimech and Ruthie (11/87), 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Goldberg, Rhoda (10/87), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Goldberg, Rich (3/88), 1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Goldberg, Sandra and Marshal (10/14/88-10/22/88), 1988 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Golden, Linda, Joel and Stewart, May 1988 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Golden, Louise and Bill, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Goldman, Alvin ('87), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Goldman, Andrew A.; Greenblatt, Samuel J.; Weiner, Richard N., November 8-19, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Goldman, Bob and Jocelyn (7/25/75-7/28/75), 1975 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Goldmark, Rabbi Lawrence, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Goldmintz, Rabbi Jay (12/24/87-1/4/88), 1988 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Goldstein, Jerrod (7/87), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Goldstein, Joshua, Rabbi and Alexander, Stephen F., December 7-17, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Goldstein, Norman and Stein, Mel (9/87), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Goldstein, Rabbi David and Shannie (12/22/86-1/1/87), undated, 1981-1984, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Goldstein-Balt, Sol (4/12/??-4/22/??), undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Goldstone, Marcia (8/30/86-9/10/86), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Golomb, Betty and David (11/76), 1976 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Golub, Paul (8/17/89-9/4/89), 1989 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Goodfriend, Cantor (Fall '86?), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Goodman, Alan and Gwen (4/15/74), 1974 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Goodman, Dr. David and Elaine, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Goodman, Micah (7/84), 1984 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Goodman, Mr. and Mrs. Alan (7/75), 1975 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Goodman, William W. (9/86) with Photos, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Goot, Robert and Edry (6/87), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Gordon, Marge and Bob (7/6/75-7/20/75), 1975 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Gordon, Mr. and Mrs. Harvard G./Schwartz, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (6/83), undated, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Gordon, Mr. and Mrs. Ralph (11/73), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Gorelick, Todd (6/2/89-6/19/89) (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Goren, Jerry; Johnson, Bob (7/3/86-7/11/86), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Gorin, David (9/8/86-9/16/86), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Gorin, Rabbi Howard and Gold, Rabbi Michael (12/11/88-12/21/88), 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Gorlin Lassner, Daniel (12/87-1/88), 1988 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Gotlieb, Evon and Jerry (11/12/86-11/24/86), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Gottlieb, Lily and Michael (8/7/85-8/23/85), 1985 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - Graber, Alan, Dr. (Medical Reports on Refuseniks), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Greenbaum, Donald and Shelley (11/23/88-12/4/88), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Greenberg, Cheryl (1/1/87-1/17/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Greenberg, Jack and Deborah/Keith, Damon J. and Rachel B. (6/2/76-6/4/76), 1976 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Greenland, Leo (5/85), 1985 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Greenspan, Mireet (1/17/88-1/31/88), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Gribetz, Donald (Summer '74), 1974, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Gribetz, Dr. Donald (12/75), 1975 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Grinspoon, Harold and Troderman, Diane (9/11/86-9/12/86), 1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Groner, Oscar; Simon, Matthew; Luxemburg, Jack; Essrog, Seymour (12/18/88-12/30/88), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Gross, Lois and Leonard (9/88), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Gross, Margola and Morris (3/29/88-4/12/88), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Grossberg, Penina and Elkins, Jonathan (12/29/86-1/11/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Grossman, Grace Cohen (5/18/77-5/28/77), 1977 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Grossman, Mark and Bullen, Anne (5/22/87-6/5/87), undated, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Gunner, Haim and Yaffa (3/16/77-3/29/77), undated, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Gurevich, Dita ('89), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Gurvis, Mark (9/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Guthman, Sidney, Rabbi, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Gutin, Jules/Savenor, Charles/Shrerer, Meir (5/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Haas, Gregory and Tybe (7/4/87-7/15/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Haber, Elaine (10/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Halbert, Janet and Frantz, Bob (11/13/86-11/23/86), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Hallem, Timi Anyon, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Halperin, Samuel (11/71), 1971 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Harris, David (9/81), 1981 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Hartman, Rita and Jerry (8/10/89-8/29/89), 1989 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Harwick, Sarah (7/75), 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Heilman, Boaz (10/87), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Heller, Hannah (6/2/83-6/19/83) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Heller, Shelly, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Heller, Stephen R. (6/20/77-7/21/77), 1977 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Heller, Steve, Shelly, Josh and Adam (7/4/86-7/18/86), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Hellman, Judy and Kaplan, Elizabeth (10/87), 1987 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Hellmann, Dr. Mark (11/87), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Helzner, Robyn and Greene, Phyllis (10/9/88-10/19/88) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Henderson, Marjorie Beth (Manuscript on Vladimir and Mariya Slepak, based on the trip to USSR, 250 pages) [1 of 2], 1987 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Henderson, Marjorie Beth (Manuscript on Vladimir and Mariya Slepak, based on the trip to USSR, 250 pages) [2 of 2], 1987 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Hersh, Andrew and Kentor, Eric (8/27/86-9/7/86), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Herz, Gert and Fred (8/26/89-9/17/89), 1989 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Herzog, Mitchell W. (4/77), 1977 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Heutlinger, Mark; Cutler, Bonnie (9/6/85-9/17/85), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Hill, Rabbi David (9/13/81), 1981 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Hiller, Arthur (1/76), 1976 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Hindes, Sally, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Hirsch, Carol (1/12/84-1/23/84), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Hirsch, David and Ellen (12/27/87-1/3/88), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Hirsch, Dorothy (5/16/81-5/24/81), 1981 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Hirschfield, Dr. Jay (10/74), 1974 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Hoffman, Bee and Phillip (9/88), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Hollander, Norman, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Holtzman, Mr. and Mrs. Irwin, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Hornestay, Shirley (1/17/88-1/31/88), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Horowitz, Rabbi Shlomo and Shifra (8/26/84-9/9/84), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Hurwitz, Larry, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Idinopulos, Thomas, March 10-20, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Indianer, Leonard E. (5/1/76-5/7/76), 1976 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Ingerman, Dr. Arthur and Rosalie (8/7/88-8/20/88), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Irmas, undated (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Israel, Richard J. and Sherry R. (5/19/74-6/12/74) (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Jacobson, Charlotte; Sondheim, Evelyn (9/10/85-9/23/85), 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Jacobson, Debbie and Kranzberg, Shirlee (8/89), 1989 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Jacoby, Ken and Meta Joy (6/16/89-7/1/89), 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Jaffe, Clara (10/4/88-10/24/88), 1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Jaffe, Rabbi Howard (1/3/87-1/11/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Jick, Leon A. and Todd D. (4/13/76-4/27/76), 1976 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Ben, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Joseph, Samuel K., April 10-20, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Joyce, Professor Ellen (5/15/76-5/29/76), 1976 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Kabakow, Dr. (1987), undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Kadosh, Aviva and Huberman, Freda (11/26/87-12/6/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Kadushin, Lois and Adrian (7/85), 1985 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Kagan, Irving and Shirley (10/16/84-10/28/84), 1984 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Kahn, Kathryn and Clifford, July 22-August 2, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Kalin, Ruth and Marvin, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Kameny, Nat, Ruth, and Leslie (3/1/74-3/9/74), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Kamilar, Barbara and Abouaf, Sandy (10/6/87-10/18/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Kamilar, Barbara, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Kaminetsky, Simon; Schwartz; Leibowitz, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Kamlet, Art and Regina; Sher, Herbert and Bonnie (8/12/87-8/24/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Kaplan, Lily C. (7/7/74-7/21/74), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Kaplan, Rabbi and B'nai B'rith (3/13/89-3/22/89), 1989 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Kaplan, Stanley A. (7/79), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Kaplan, Warren (3/18/87-3/28/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Karlow, Mary Ann, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Karp, Herbert, Dr., and Hazel, June 28-July 14, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Kash, Kaygey (3/27/77-4/5/77), 1977 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Kasirer, Naomi, Mark and Suri (6/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Kasner, Martha and Victor/Goldblatt, David and Elaine (8/14/85-8/29/85), 1985 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Kassel, Charles and Mimi (7/6/85-7/28/85), 1985 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Katleman, Ferne, June 19-21, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Katz Wasser Amy and Buff, Hillary, April 24-May 4, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Katz, George, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Kaufman, Lynn (8/87), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Kaye, David and Weinblatt, Stuart (10/88), 1988 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Kaymen, Diana (8/10/85-8/23/85), 1985 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Keller, Diane; Mirkin, Stu (3/8/80-3/15/80), 1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Keyserling, William David/Denis, Howard Allen (7/26/84-8/5/84), 1978, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Kideckel, Lana and Warmflash, Phil (10/12/89-10/23/89), 1989 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Kiewe, Jerome M., June 1988 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Kingsley, Rabbi Ralph (9/2/84), 1984 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Klein, Linda (5/25/86-6/8/86), 1986 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Kligfeld, Michael and Caryl, March 17-31, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Klutznick, Philip (12/84), 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Koenigsberg, Clara (4/29/85-5/13/85), 1985 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Kohn, Herbert A. and Betty (3/23/75-4/6/75), 1975 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Kohn, Rabbi Douglas and Hirschenfang, Cantor Gail (2/89), 1989 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Kohrman, Margery (9/81), 1981 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Kohrman/Minkoff (9/81), 1981 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Kolatch, David (6/88), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Kolker, Fabian (6/9/87-6/20/87), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Kolko, Simeon, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Kopp, Martin and Frances (6/87), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Koransky, Carol, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Koransky, Jerry, undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Koschitzsky, David and Sarina (3/87), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Kostiner, Priscilla (3/87), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Kotlyar, Sergey (8/89), 1989 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Kowalsky, Rabbi Sholem B. (9/79-10/79), 1979 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Kracauer, Dr. Randall (12/75-1/76), 1976 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Krantz, Dr. David and Douma, Dr. Marsha (11/6/88-11/14/88), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Kreiger, Sylvia and Howard (son) (6/24/89-7/1/89), 1989 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Krisman, Esther (9/18/88-10/5/88), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Krisman, Esther (9/19/88-10/5/88) (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Kronish, Mr. and Mrs. Herbert (7/77), undated (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Kroopnick, Lianne (5/24/89-6/8/89), 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Krug, Rabbi John A. (1/89), 1989 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Krugman, Dorothy (8/87), 1987 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Krupp, Peter, April 1988 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Kuhr, Murray D. (8/14/78-8/28/78), 1978 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Kurlander, Lawrence and Wall, Patrick (4/6/85-4/14/85), 1985 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Kushner, Rabbi Steven (2/14/87-2/26/87), undated, 1986-1987 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Kushnir, Steven and Marilyn (3/87), undated, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Labes, Ellen and Jim, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Lakritz, Isaac, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Lalak, Adrienne C. (10/87-11/87), 1987 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Lander, Frank and Kathy (10/84), undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Landerman Goldberg, Emily, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Landis, Donald and Betsy (10/12/87-10/25/87), 1987 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Landis, Marc (National Law Students Network) (2/87), 1987 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Lane, Dorothy (7/17/83-7/31/83), 1983 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Lane, Eileen, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Lax, Melvin and Judy, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Lazarus, Jeffrey and Shelly ('89), 1989 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Lefkowitz, Jerry (5/2/77-5/15/77), 1977 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Lehiman, Dr. and Mrs. Philip (6/3/85-6/16/85), undated (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Leibowitz, Bruce (3/87, 3/88), 1987-1988 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Leibowitz, Shira (12/86-1/87), undated, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Leisch, Nancy and Greg (3/13/1976-3/20/76) (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Lender, Helaine and Marvin, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Lerman, David (8/20/75-9/3/75), 1975, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Lerman, Ina and Larry, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Lerner, Allan and Nancy, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Lerner, Allan and Phil (4/86), 1986 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Lerner, Lawrence I. and Dresner, Rabbi Israel (1/31/88-2/11/88), 1988 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Lerner, Lenore and Maximilian, August 12-29, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Lerner, Mimi, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Lesser, Linda and Warren; Grossman, Barbara and Gerry (10/6/87-10/12/87), 1987 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Levenson, Dena and Steven (5/27/84-6/12/84), 1984 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Levin, Bernie and Lenore (11//84), 1984 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Levin, Karen and Joel (7/18/76-8/1/76), 1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Levin, Mace, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Levin, Rick and Louise (1987), undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Levine, Hal (2/81-3/81), 1981 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Levine, Julius (8/15/85-8/25/85), 1985 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Karen and Joe, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Levine, Noah (9/87-10/87), 1987 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Levine, Ruth (5/77), 1977 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Levinson, Burt and Anita (11/74), 1974 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Levinstone, Millie and Bert (3/23/74), 1974 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Levitt, Sheldon and Barbara (7/89), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Levkowitz, Dr. and Mrs. Jack (5/15/85-5/30/85), 1985 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Lewin, Nathan and family (7/89), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Lewis, Jerry (12/73) (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Lewit, Abigail (7/88), 1988 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Liacouras, Peter J.; Caine, Burton (12/77), 1977 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Licht, Richard A. (4/30/89-5/7/89), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Lichtman, Robert; Freeman, Steven (10/4/82-10/11/82), 1983 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Lieb, Rabbi David S. (4/1/89-4/11/89), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Liebowitz, Estelle and Jerry (10/25/86-11/1/86), 1986 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Lipnick, Rabbi Bernard and Harriet (4/10/84-4/26/84), 1984 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Lippert, Jules R. (7/27/73-8/1/73, 12/76, 10/78), 1973, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Lippitz, Riki and Schechter, John (6/89), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Lipstadt, Deborah, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Liskov, Helen and San, and Kaplan, Betty and Elias (8/84), undated, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Liston, Seema and Weiss, Gayle (10/88), 1988 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Litvan, Arkady (Summer '89), 1989 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Litwack, Wendy (4/11/88-4/21/88), 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Litwack, Wendy and Wolfe, Sharon (12/78), 1979 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Lokash, Brent and David, Eytan (8/2/88-8/17/88), 1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Lombrosso, Mona (9/88), 1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Lookstein, Haskel, Rabbi (5/87), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Lookstein, Rabbi and Mrs. Haskel (9/16/75-10/2/75), 1976 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Loveman, Mr. and Mrs. S. Michael/Frankel, Burton and Rita (9/86), 1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Lowenstein, Michael and Elaine/Taragin, Daniel and Leah (7/82), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Lublin, Sheri, March 16-30, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Lukaczer, Lillian and Moses (6/75), 1975 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Lux, Margie and Ed (10/86), 1986 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Maisel, Blanch, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Maltzman, Marshall and Ruth (1/1/87-1/11/87), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Mandeles, Laura (11/9/86-11/20/86) (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Manekofsky, Irene (11/14/74-11/26/74), 1974 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Mann, Theodore (10/86), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Mann, Theodore (6/81), 1981 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Mannis, Sam and Vicky, August 1988 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Mansheim, Renee (9/1984), undated, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Marans, Rabbi and Mrs. Arnold B. (8/31/87-9/13/87), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Marcuse, Peter and Frances, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Margulies, Fred (11/10/77-11/21/77), 1977 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Markman, Ruth and Bernard (5/23/89-6/20/89), 1989 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Marpet, Richard and Nussen, Steven and Plotkin, Carol (11/86), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Matlow, P. T. (10/86-11/86), (12/89), 1986, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Mccormic, Larry, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - McEnvoy, Dan and Greenberger, Howard (6/1980) (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - McGuigan, Jack, undated (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Meier, Ron and Joyce (3/27/77-4/11/77), 1977 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Meirovich, Harvey, Rabbi (3/87), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Mervis, Michael (3/82), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Meskin, Annette (Hadassah), March 3-16, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Meth, Robert, J., 1987, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Meyers, Harriet and Milgram, Miriam (12/87), 1988 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Milgram, Tammy, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Miller, Michael, Rabbi (4/83), undated, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Miller, Naomi and David, (8/87-9/87), 1987 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Minnick, Bari A. (1/9/89-1/19/89) (Box 68, Folder 36)